cbtopsites.com 2012-05-06

# Privacy Policy for CBTopSites.com

[ ](http://cbtopsites.com/ "CB Top Sites .com Main Page") |  * eBooks & Software Directory     
* 70000 Instant Downloads     
* Search or Browse Categories   |  * 100% Satisfaction Guarantee  
* 60 Day Refund Guarantee  
* 100% Safe & Secure   
---|---|---  
  
The privacy of our visitors to CBTopSites.com is important to us. At CBTopSites.com, we recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use and visit CBTopSites.com, and how we safeguard your information. We never sell your personal information to third parties. CBTopSites.com is committed to maintaining the privacy of personal information that you provide to us when using any of our online services. This Privacy Policy describes how we treat the information we receive when you transmit data through CBTopSites.com . 

## Web Form Information

When you submit information to CBTopSites.com to open an account, we may collect personally identifiable information from you that may include your name, email address etc. We do not knowingly collect personal information from persons under the age of eighteen. 

## Web Site Usage Information

We automatically collect IP addresses and Web site usage information from you when you access any of our online services. This information helps us evaluate how our visitors and subscribers use and navigate our Web sites on an aggregate basis, including but not limited to, the number and frequency of visitors and subscribers to each web page and the length of their visits. 

## How We Use Information Collected

We may use information in the following ways:   
* To perform the actions for which you specifically provided the information. * To register you as a client and establish an account for you. * To send you email notifications about our new or existing CBTopSites.com products and services, special offers, or to otherwise contact you. * To enhance existing features or develop new features, products and services. 

Except as specifically set forth in this Privacy Policy, we will not share your personally identifiable information with any entity outside of CBTopSites.com .   
We may disclose and use personally identifiable information in special circumstances where it is necessary to enforce our service agreements or terms of use. We may also disclose or use your personal information when we, in good faith, believe that the law may require us to do so. 

## Security

The personally identifiable information we collect about you is stored in limited access servers. We maintain safeguards to protect the security of these servers and your personally identifiable information. We retain personally identifiable information only as long as necessary to complete a purchase, thwart fraud, provide customer service, or maintain your account with us. 

## Log Files

As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider, such as AOL or Shaw Cable), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site. 

## Cookies and Web Beacons 

1) of limited duration, 2) less than 5KB in length, 3) only visible to CBTopSites.com web servers   
We define a cookie as any string of data that is automatically stored on your computer upon access to our online services. CBTopSites.com employs cookies to assign temporary identification numbers to machines that access our web servers. This information enables us to deliver faster service to our subscribers, prevent denial of service attacks on our systems,   
We do use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit our site. This could include only showing you a popup once in your visit, or the ability to login to some of our features, such as forums. CBTopSites.com cookies are devoid of any personally identifiable information. We also use third party advertisements on CBTopSites.com to support our site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for geotargeting purposes (showing New York real estate ads to someone in New York, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites). You can choose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts. Deleting cookies does not mean you are permanently opted out of any advertising program. Unless you have settings that disallow cookies, the next time you visit a site running the advertisements, a new cookie will be added. 

## Policy Modifications

We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time. We will post any changes here, so be sure to check back periodically. Comments and Questions. 

If you have any questions, comments or concerns about our Privacy Policy, you may email to admin at cbtopsites.com. 

* * *

email to: admin at cbtopsites.com © 2005-11 CBTopSites.com All Rights Reserved.   [Privacy Policy](http://cbtopsites.com/privacy_policy.php) [Webmasters and Affiliates](http://cbtopsites.com/site/downlod "Webmasters and Affiliates earn money")

Disclaimer : CBTopSites.com directory updates the details about Privacy Policy for CBTopSites.com sites from the Clickbank datafeed or the publisher websites or blogs. We do not directly provide Privacy Policy for CBTopSites.com downloads, CD or DVD, pirated torrent files, nulled or cracked versions, or links from file sharing sites like rapidshare, megaupload or mediafire etc. Direct Download links are available on the product web sites after purchase. 

Link to This Page
